Preliminary Guide to the Marine Laboratory Records, 1931-2006 UA.18.03.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2018.0075
  - Photo album of R/V Eastward, 1963-1964 (Box 19)
    black-and-white prints
  - Eastward Photos, circa 1964 (Box 19)
  - Publicity [includingDUML News], circa 1982-1986 (Box 19)
  - Photographs-publicity, 1989 (Box 19)
  - Publicity, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Publicity, 1992 (Box 19)
  - R/V Cape Hatteras photos (Box 19)
    color and black-and-white
  - Publicity, circa 1976 (Box 19)
  - Open Grounds Farm, Inc--Publicity, 1975 (Box 19)
  - Publicity, circa 1974 (Box 19)
  - Hurricane Floyd Press, 1999 (Box 19)
  - Newspaper Clippings, DUML, circa 1969 (Box 19)
  - Eastward Photos (Box 19)
    color and black-and-white prints and negatives and contact sheets
  - Delaware (Univ. of) Protest (Box 19)
  - Photographs--R/V Eastward, Construction (Box 19)
    black-and-white
  - loose negatives (Box 19)
  - unlabeled folder of photos (Box 20)
  - red album of photos, circa 1990 (Box 20)
  - publicity, 1979 (Box 20)
  - Publicity, 1980 (Box 20)
  - Publicity, 1981 (Box 20)
  - Artwork (R/V Cape Hatteras) (Box 20)
  - unlabeled (group photo) (Box 20)
  - unlabeled folder of photos (Box 20)
  - certificates (Box 20)
  - loose packets of snapshot prints/negatives (Box 20)
  - from box labeled "pre-Scott" (Box 20)
  - unidentified negatives and contact sheets (Box 20)
  - loose negatives, prints, and slides (Box 20)
  - negatives (Box 20)
  - contacts (Box 20)
  - People (Box 20)
  - ship pictures (Box 20)
  - Bookie's photos (Box 20)
  - polaroid negatives and letter (Box 20)
  - Yale Club slide show (Box 20)
  - DUML Slide Presentation script (Box 20)
  - DUML Christmas card [may be inaccurate] contains assortment of negatives and contact sheets] (Box 20)
  - Misc old Scott photo files/jobs, [illegible]-90s early (Box 20)
  - UPI (Box 21)
  - unlabeled envelope of photos (Box 21)
  - NC Maritime Museum, 1988 (Box 21)
    black-and-white negatives
  - New World Publishers (Box 21)
    black-and-white prints, slides
  - Turnstile (Box 21)
  - Brown's Boat Pix, Concordia, 1987 October (Box 21)
    negatives, slides
  - Inlet Inn, 1985 (Box 21)
    negatives, prints, slides
  - Southern Skimmer, 1985 (Box 21)
    negatives, prints
  - WED-Enterprises, EPCOT (Box 21)
  - Medical Products Search, Inc.--MPB, 1988 (Box 21)
  - Bradley Phyle (Box 21)
    negatives
  - News-Times Stepper Associates Inc (Box 21)
  - Russ Russell, 1984 January 30 (Box 21)
    negatives, prints, contact sheets
  - Omar Sails (Box 21)
    prints, negatives
  - Open Grounds (Box 21)
    slides
  - NandO photos, 1987 (Box 21)
  - Boating Records, 1989 (Box 21)
  - Al Wadsworth-"Mary Catherine", 1989 May (Box 21)
    negatives, contact sheets
  - Resume (Box 21)
  - Mirror on Maritime, 1989 September 10 (Box 21)
  - BW contacts from Wind Jam, Atlantic Beach, 1987 August 08 (Box 21)
    contact sheets, prints
  - SECCA Show, 1987 March (Box 21)
  - This Week Magazine and CCNT Group Shot, 1991 (Box 21)
  - Clippings (Box 21)
  - Jim Willis-Architect (Box 21)
  - Bridge Accident - Terry Buck (Box 21)
  - Tabbie Nance - Schools, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Bradley Phyle (Box 21)
  - Davi Cohen (Box 21)
  - Misc outside pix, 1992 (Box 21)
  - Steve Goodspeed, 1991 December (Box 21)
  - NCMM Brodum pictures, 1990 December (Box 21)
    negatives and prints
  - Andrew and Kuske, 1990 November 08 (Box 21)
  - Baldheaded Mens Convention, Holiday Inn, for London Observer, 1990 September 08 (Box 21)
  - Morehead City proofs, 1996 January 10 (Box 21)
  - Unknown Tongues, 1995 March (Box 21)
  - Misc photo jobs, 1997 (Box 21)
  - unlabeled sheet of slides (Box 21)
  - Misc Parker Boats (Box 21)
  - Misc Outside jobs, 1994 (Box 21)
  - Cosen Group Pic, 1994 June 09 (Box 21)
  - CCNT group photo and pix of Walter, 1994 December 15 (Box 21)
  - Morehead City Council pix, 1994 January 11 (Box 21)
  - Morehead City Town Council, 1992 January (Box 21)
  - Parker Boats, 1992 September (Box 21)
  - Parker Boats (Box 21)
  - Gerald's group, 1993 January 11 (Box 21)
  - 2 loose slide sleeves (Box 21)
  - CCNT, 1993 (Box 21)
  - Cosen Group photos, 1993 June 10 (Box 21)
  - Linda Staab, 1993 January 26 (Box 21)
  - MCPD Group shot, 1993 July 21 (Box 21)
  - assorted DUML publications/print materials, 1940s-2000s (Box 21)
  - DUML photos, some mounted on cardboard (slightly oversize) (Box 22)
  - uninventoried files (Box 23)
  - Photos-Sugar Hudson (Box 24)
  - Conference on Marine Invertibrate Larvae, 1967 (Box 24)
  - A proposal for the Development of DUML, 1965 (Box 24)
  - blue folder of assorted photos and letters, circa 1940s? (Box 24)
  - green folder with various 1960s correspondence (Box 24)
  - binder with uninventoried slides, and photo staff directory (Box 24)
  - DUML print materials (Box 24)
  - Bookhout glass slides (Box 24)
  - uninventoried snapshots (Box 24)
  - Duke-UNC Oceanographic consortium newsletter, 1988-1998 (Box 24)
  - Pilkey memo, 1979 (Box 24)
  - Marine Biomed Center newsletter, 1980-1981 (Box 24)
  - DUML Currents, 1980-1981 (Box 24)
  - photo snapshots (Box 25)
  - VHS tapes (Box 26)
  - photo snapshots (Box 26)
  - slides, prints, photo flashcards (of every employee), glass plate negative, negatives, mostly 1940s-1950s (Box 27)
  - 1KB, 2KB, 3KB, 4KB, miscellaneous box of slides (Box 28)
  - 5KB, 6KB, 8KB, 9KB, 9KB-2 (Box 29)
  - 10KB, 11KB, 12KB, 13KB. 15 (Box 30)
  - SB1, SB2, SB3 (Box 31)
  - SB4, SB5, SB6 (Box 32)
  - SB7, SB8, SB9 (Box 33)
  - SB10, SB11, SB12 (Box 34)
  - SB13, SB14, SB15 (Box 35)
  - SB16, SB17, SB18 (Box 36)
  - SB19, SB20, SB21 (Box 37)
  - SB22, SB23, SB24 (Box 38)
  - SB25, SB26, SB27 (Box 39)
  - SB28 (Box 40)
  - Contributions of the DUML volumes, #1-331 (Box 41)
  - Contributions of the DUML volumes, #332-547 (Box 42)
  - volume of work done wholly or in part at DUML, 1938-1940s (Box 42)
  - Donors: Foundations (Box 43)
  - Donors: Prospects (Box 43)
  - Donors: Corporate Associates (Box 43)
  - Donors: Corporate Research (Box 43)
  - Donors: Donor Correspondence A-B (Box 43)
  - Donors: Donor Correspondence C-Hi (Box 44)
  - Donors: Donor Correspondence Ho-Or (Box 45)
  - Donors: Donor Correspondence Os-Sa (Box 46)
  - Donors: Donor Correspondence Sc-Z (Box 47)
  - Annual Fund: Annual Fund, circa 1983 (Box 47)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Advisory Committee meetings, 1970-1988 (Box 48)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Board list, pre-2007 (Box 48)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Marine Lab Associates (Box 48)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Fundraising (Box 48)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Duke Club of Wilmington (Box 48)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Florida Fundraising (Box 48)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Meeting Agendas, 1994, 2000, 2002 (Box 48)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Meeting Agendas, 2000 (Box 49)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Members and Meetings (Box 49)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Board bios (Box 49)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Advisory Board Nominations Committee (Box 49)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Advisory Board Community Services Committee (Box 49)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Advisory Board: General (Box 49)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Advisory Board, April 1994 (Box 49)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Meetings, 1986, 1987, 1989, 1998, 1999 (Box 49)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Development: Proposals by Staff and Advisory Board Members, 1986 (Box 49)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: E-Miscellaneous (Box 49)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Faculty Invited to Board (Box 49)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Appointment- HR format (Box 49)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Meetings, 2003, 2000 (Box 49)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Meetings, 2005 (Box 50)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Nicholas School Board of Visitors meeting, 2004 (Box 50)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Meeting, 2005 (Box 50)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Nicholas School Board of Visitors meeting, 2005 (Box 50)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Meetings, 2005-2006 (Box 50)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Miscellaneous (Box 50)
  - Development: Endowments, circa 2000 (Box 50)
  - Development: Endostat, 1997-1999 (Box 50)
  - Development: Endowed chairs/appointments, 1985 (Box 50)
  - Development: Endowments (3 folders), 1985, undated (Box 50)
  - Development: Development: Dean's report on the state of the School of the Environment, 1995 (Box 50)
  - Development: Development (Box 50)
  - Development: Development office: Duke (Box 50)
  - Development: Development plan: original (Box 50)
  - Development: Development Report (Box 50)
  - Development: Development projects (Box 50)
  - Development: General (Box 50)
  - Development: Development Agenda (Box 50)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Advisory Board Campaign Goals (Box 51)
  - DUML Advisory Committee/Board: Minutes: Advisory Board (Box 51)
  - General: Hiring/position planning [Abrogation document folder] (Box 51)
  - General: Unlabeled (Box 51)
  - General: Chancellor's Advisory Cmte for Cooperative programs (2 folders), 1979 (Box 51)
  - General: letter to chancellor re dorms, grad school etc., 1977 (Box 51)
  - General: Currents newsletter, 1974-1980 (Box 51)
  - General: DUNCOC Duke-UNC Oceanographic constorital (many folders), 1980s (Box 51)
  - General: DUNCOC Pier and Policy Board (Box 51)
  - General: New research vessel Consortium (Box 51)
  - General: Correspondence Duke and Beaufort Oceanography (2 folders) (Box 51)
  - General: Correspondence (Box 51)
  - General: Correspondence (Box 52)
  - General: Correspondence- National Science Foundation (2 foolders, ovesized drawings) (Box 52)
  - General: Boat Dedication (Box 52)
  - General: Correspondence Potter, McArthur, and Simpson (Vessel) (Box 52)
  - General: Correspondence -Internal Oceanography Vessel (Box 52)
  - General: Correspondence - Sturgeon Bay (Oceanography Vessel) (Box 52)
  - General: Correspondence - Miscellaenous (Oceanography Vessel) - Newton (Box 52)
  - General: Environmental Sciences Teaching Center (Box 52)
  - General: EA Retreat, March 2000 (Box 52)
  - General: Environmental Science and Policy Committee (Box 52)
  - General: Faculty Bios (Box 52)
  - General: Fairly Dickinson (Box 52)
  - General: Faculty Census for SOE (Box 52)
  - General: Faculty Meetings (Box 52)
  - General: Faculty Newsletters (Box 52)
  - General: Bonaventura, Joseph and Celia (Box 53)
    Conditions Governing Access
    RESTRICTED NEEDS REVIEW
  - General: Bookout, C. G., 8 folders (Box 53)
  - General: Costlow, John DeForest (Box 53)
  - General: Fluke, Donald J. (Box 53)
  - General: Forward, Richard, 2 folders (Box 53)
  - General: Kirby-Smith, William, 2 folders (Box 53)
  - General: Orbach, Michael, 2 folders (Box 53)
  - General: Photographs (Box 53)
  - General: Ramus Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 53)
  - General: Director correspondence (Box 54)
  - General: 50th Anniversary material, 6 folders (Box 54)
  - General: Marine Biomedical Center (Box 54)
  - General: Storehouse Building and Marine Laboratory (Box 55)
  - General: Director, DU Marine Lab (Box 55)
  - General: Bridge: Duke Marine Lab (Box 55)
  - General: Marine Biological Lab, 1963 June-undated (Box 55)
  - General: Marine Laboratory Matters (Box 55)
  - General: Reports, 3 folders (Box 55)
  - General: Unlabeled, 2 folders (Box 55)
  - General: NSF Marine Lab Directors report (Box 55)
  - General: NSF Marine Lab Directors report, 1981 (Box 55)
  - General: NSF Statements and meetings, 6 folders (Box 55)
  - General: NSF Marine Lab Directors report, 1981 (Box 55)
  - General: NSF Lab Direcotrs comments and questionnaires, answers (Box 55)
  - General:, 1981 Fall (Box 55)
  - General: NSF Marine Lab Directors report, August 5 deadline (Box 55)
  - General: NSF Marine Lab directors workshop, 1980 May (Box 55)
  - General: NSF Marine Lab directors workshop background for writing proposal, 1980 May (Box 55)
  - General: Unlabeled (Box 55)
  - General: NSF Marine Lab Directors: revision, 1980 Fall (Box 55)
  - General: NSF Marine Lab directors workshop: list of participants, 1980 (Box 55)
  - General: NSF Marine Lab Director's report, 1980 July (Box 55)
  - General: NSF Marine Lab Director's workshop: letters from directors, 1980 May (Box 56)
  - General: MSF marine director's report second revision mailing list (Box 56)
  - General: NSF marine lab director's workshop: copies of proposals, 1980 May (Box 56)
  - General: Unlabeled, 2 folders (Box 56)
  - General: unlabeled correspondence (Box 56)
  - General: NSOE bylaws (Box 56)
  - General: NSOE divisions (Box 56)
  - General: SOE (Box 56)
  - General: NSOE strategic plan (Box 56)
  - General: NOAA/DUML MOU, 1980 (Box 56)
  - General: RTB: realignment of pceanography (Box 56)
  - General: DUML oceanography CUEA personnel Allred/Johnson (Box 56)
  - General: unlabeled (Box 56)
  - General: Pilkey, Orrin, 3 folders (Box 56)
  - General: unfoldered Pilkey correspondence (Box 56)
  - General: DUML container-ized building oceanographic floorplans (Box 56)
  - General: Rachel Carson estuarine sanctuary, 6 folders (Box 56)
  - General: Estuarine research reserve (Box 56)
  - General: DU president's office (Box 56)
  - General: Self study university (Box 56)
  - General: Sewage (Marine Lab) (Box 56)
  - General: SIMBOL (Box 56)
  - General: Board, 2006 Fall (Box 56)
  - General: Board meeting, 2003 Fall (Box 56)
  - General: Board meeting, 2004 Spring (Box 56)
  - General: Board meeting, 2004 Fall (Box 56)
  - General: Board meeting, 2002 Fall (Box 56)
  - General: Board meeting, 2003 Spring (Box 56)
  - General: Board meeting, 2002 Spring; 2 folders (Box 56)
  - General: Board meeting, 2000 Fall (Box 57)
  - General: Board meeting, 2001 November (Box 57)
  - General: unlabeled (Box 57)
  - General: Vernberg, F.J. correspondence, 1964 January-unknown (Box 57)
  - General: Wilbur, Dr. correspondence, 1963 October-unknown (Box 57)
  - General: unlabeled correspondence (Box 57)
  - Facilities: Annexation (Box 57)
  - Facilities: Bridge, 6 folders (Box 57)
  - Facilities: Bridge reports, 2 items (Box 57)
  - Facilities: Bradley International House, 6 folders (Box 57)
  - Facilities: Facilities audit (Box 58)
  - Facilities: Annexation (Box 58)
  - Facilities: unlabeled (Box 58)
  - Facilities: Colonial Apartments (Box 58)
  - Facilities: Carpenter property (Box 58)
  - Facilities: Bridge: loads (Box 58)
  - Facilities: Colonial Apartments/Carpenter, 12 folders (Box 58)
  - Facilities: Bradley (Box 58)
  - Facilities: unlabeled (Box 58)
  - Facilities: Quitclaim deed (Box 58)
  - Facilities: Prytherch and abandonment, 3 folders (Box 58)
  - Facilities: Pivers Island (Box 58)
  - Facilities: DUML Director's report, 1961 June-1963 June (Box 58)
  - Facilities: Colonial Apartments/Carpenter, 2 folders (Box 58)
  - Facilities: Davis House, 2 folders (Box 58)
  - Facilities: C.G. Bookout correspondence (Box 59)
  - Facilities: Davis house renovations, 5 folders (Box 59)
  - Facilities: Dining hall renovations, 2 folders (Box 59)
  - Facilities: HUD proposals (Box 59)
  - Facilities: unlabeled (Box 59)
  - Facilities: History of additions (Box 59)
  - Facilities: unlabeled, 4 folders (Box 59)
  - Facilities: Library (Box 59)
  - Facilities: New vessel (Box 59)
  - Facilities: new maintenance building (Box 59)
  - Facilities: Storm of the Century (Box 59)
  - Facilities: OST naming gifts (Box 59)
  - Facilities: OCC plaques (Box 59)
  - Facilities: OSTC (Box 59)
  - Facilities: OSTC donors (Box 59)
  - Facilities: Gache scilpture (Box 59)
  - Facilities: Fundraising (Box 59)
  - Facilities: AU OSTC (Box 59)
  - Facilities: Marine Lab oceanic research vessel (Box 60)
  - Facilities: Marine Lab research facility (Box 60)
  - Facilities: NASA instrument of waiver AB (Box 60)
  - Facilities: EPA sea water facility (Box 60)
  - Facilities: DUML service complex (Box 60)
  - Facilities: ML Carolina Power and Light Company (Box 60)
  - Facilities: ML library/auditorium building (Box 60)
  - Facilities: Student green group (Box 60)
  - Facilities: OSTC evolution of (Box 60)
  - Facilities: OSTC systems (Box 60)
  - Facilities: OSTC (valinda) (Box 60)
  - Facilities: OSTC AU and furniture (Box 60)
  - Facilities: unlabeled (Box 60)
  - Facilities: budgets and financing (Box 60)
  - Facilities: LEED certification (Box 60)
  - Facilities: unlabeled (Box 60)
  - Facilities: blueprints (Box 60)
  - Facilities: CP&L (Box 60)
  - Facilities: Energy information (Box 60)
  - Facilities: inground tanks (Box 60)
  - Facilities: asbestos, 2 folders (Box 60)
  - Facilities: unlabeled (Box 60)
  - Facilities: Tinsley, H. (Box 60)
  - Facilities: Five year capitalization plan (Box 60)
  - General: Newsletters, 1983 Fall-1998 Spring (Box 61)
  - General: Newsletters, 1998 Fall-1999 Fall (Box 62)
  - General: Assorted publications (Box 62)
  - General: Marine Lab Academic Progress and Comparative Data, 1989; 2 items (Box 62)
  - General: unlabeled report, 2 items (Box 62)
  - General: Board meetings, circa 2000s; 6 folders (Box 62)
  - General: DUML Report, 1980 (Box 62)
  - General: ONR High School Interest Program, circa 1990s; 7 folders (Box 62)
  - ONR HSIP 1992-1997 renewal grant (Box 63)
  - ONR HSIP annual report, 1992 (Box 63)
  - Intern questionaires (returned, 1992 (Box 63)
  - ONR HSIP, 1992 (Box 63)
  - ONR HSIP orals, reports, 1992 (Box 63)
  - ONR HSIP applications, 1992 (Box 63)
  - ONR HSIP letters of thanks/recommendations, 1992 (Box 63)
  - ONR HSIP advertising, 1992 (Box 63)
  - ONR HSIP end form, orals schedule, 1993 (Box 63)
  - ONR HSIP Apprentice Info forms, 1993 (Box 63)
  - ONR HSIP letters, 1993 (Box 63)
  - ONR HSIP memos, 1993 (Box 63)
  - ONR HSIP letters, advs and Ints, 1993 (Box 63)
  - ONR HSIP applications, 1993 (Box 63)
  - ONR HSIP Summer intern, Karen Hardy, 1993 (Box 63)
  - ONR HSIP Advertising, 1993 (Box 63)
  - ONR HSIP Annual report, 1993 (Box 63)
  - ONR HSIP applications, 1994 (Box 63)
  - ONR HSIP letters, 1994 (Box 63)
  - ONR HSIP advertising, 1994 (Box 63)
  - ONR HSIP annual report, 1994 (Box 63)
  - ONR HSIP final report, 1992-1994 (Box 63)
  - GEO 196S.01 (O. Pilkey), 1993 Spring (Box 63)
  - GEO 196S.01 (O. Pilkey), 1992 Spring (Box 63)
  - GEO 196S.01 (O. Pilkey), 1991 Spring (Box 63)
  - GEO 196S.01 (O. Pilkey), 1990 Spring (Box 63)
  - GEO 196S.01 (O. Pilkey), 1989 Spring (Box 63)
  - McCleave Bio/200 296S.84 "Fisheries Oceanography", 1993 Spring (Box 63)
  - McCleave Bio 295.S.08/Zoo 295.S.08, 1992 Fall (Box 63)
  - T. Johnson G 109/209 G 203, 1991 Fall (Box 63)
  - T. Johnson G 109/209 G 203, 1990 Fall (Box 63)
  - Johnson Geo 203.1, 1990 Fall (Box 63)
  - Gerhart Bio 169L.01, Env 294L.01, 1992 Fall (Box 63)
  - Gerhart Bio 169L, 1992 Spring (Box 63)
  - Gerhart Bio 169L, 1991 Fall (Box 63)
  - Gerhart Bio 169L, 1990 Fall (Box 63)
  - CBI 235L Von Beneden, Bonaventura et al, 1990 summer session II (Box 63)
  - Gerhar Bio/Zoo 203L, 1990 summer session II (Box 63)
  - Bio/Zoo 203L D. Gerhart, 1991 Summer (Box 63)
  - CBI 235L Von Beneden, 1991 Summer (Box 63)
  - Bio 196S.08 Syllabus and checklist, 1992 Summer (Box 63)
  - Bio/Zoo 203L D. Gerhart, 1992 Summer (Box 63)
  - CBI 235L Von Beneden, 1992 Summer (Box 63)
  - new ourse offerings and changes, 1992 Summer-1993 Spring (Box 63)
  - Summer course enrollment stats duke vs. non-Duke, 1971-1976 (Box 63)
  - other institutions represented, 1971-1981 (Box 63)
  - Institutions represented (all progs), 1974-circa 2010s (Box 63)
  - Institutions represented in summer session, 1974-circa 2010s (Box 63)
  - Institutions represented in summer session, 1964-1971 (Box 63)
  - DUML academic curriculum/costs, 1992 (Box 63)
  - Duke calendar, 1992-1993 (Box 63)
  - curriculum/cost info, 1992 Spring-1992 Fall (Box 63)
  - Duke U schedule office updates, 1991-1992 (Box 63)
  - Calendars/schedules (Box 63)
  - DUML employee course/audit registration; continuing ed policy/info (Box 63)
  - Duke automated computer enrollment system (Box 63)
  - Duke UG academic performance reports (each semester if necessary), circa 1991 (Box 63)
  - DUGS conference travel applications, 1991-1992 (Box 63)
  - Academic programs, 1991 (Box 63)
  - academic program info for xeroxing (2 folders), 1991 (Box 63)
  - curriculum, 1991 Spring-1991 Fall (Box 63)
  - DUML academic programs, 1982-1987 (Box 63)
  - statistics, 1983 Summer (Box 63)
  - statistics and trends compiled, 1983 August (Box 63)
  - statistics, 1980-1983 (Summers) (Box 63)
  - summer courses, 1980-circa 2010s (Box 63)
  - unlabeld (Box 63)
  - annual report-academic programs etc, 1982-1983 (Box 63)
  - annual report academic programs info, 1981-1982 (Box 63)
  - Fall/spring (Box 63)
  - institutions represented other than Duke (Box 63)
  - Spring/fall distribution of majors (Box 63)
  - Spring/fall institutions represented, 1972-circa 2010s (Box 63)
  - student prerequisites for spring 1992, 1991 Fall (Box 63)
  - data, 1987 August (Box 63)
  - academic info JDC proposal to Bradley foundation, 1987 March (Box 63)
  - Data for Pew Science program in UG education (for JDC), 1987 June (Box 63)
  - Academic Program Stats, 1987 Spring (Box 64)
  - Statistics and Data report: Academic progrs and comparative stats, Grad stu/degrees, seminars, 1986 (Box 64)
  - ITPMS Final Report (Box 64)
  - NBF, 1988 Spring (Box 64)
  - NBF, 1987 Fall (Box 64)
  - NBF, 1987 Summer (Box 64)
  - Academic Programs Support, 1987 (Box 64)
  - DUML Acadmic Programs Report with Comparative Data, 1993 (Box 64)
  - APRD, 1993 (Box 64)
  - 2 unlabeled folders: participants in academic programs, 1990 (Box 64)
  - Academic Program and Comparative Data Report, 1992 (Box 64)
  - Academic Program Report, 1991 (Box 64)
  - DUML Academic Progs Report LL-W, 1990 (Box 64)
  - Undergrad Spring Term: Totals, Duke/Non-Duke, Institutions, 1972-circa 2010s (Box 64)
  - Undergrad Spring Term Acadmic Staff and Curriculum, 1972-circa 2010s (Box 64)
  - Undergraduate fall term program statistics, 1931-circa 2010s (Box 64)
  - Coop program totals, institutions, 1972-circa 2010s (Box 64)
  - Davidson College, 1983 Fall (Box 64)
  - Davidson College, 1981 Fall (Box 64)
  - Davidson College: Utilization of DUML's training facilities, 1979-circa 2010s (Box 64)
  - Saint Augustine's College, Raleigh, NC: possible semester program at DUM\ (Box 64)
  - 2 unlabeled folders: academic programs statistics (Box 64)
  - unlabeled folder: DUML update to advisory board, 1981-1982 (Box 64)
  - Advisory Committee, 1980 May (Box 64)
  - unlabeled folder: summer statistics/info, 1980 (Box 64)
  - Summer statistics, 1980 (Box 64)
  - Publications, 1980-1981 (Box 64)
  - Publications, 1970-circa 2010s (Box 64)
  - Publication info-roughs (Box 64)
  - Write up: B-263L, 1983 Summer (Box 64)
  - Flyer BOT 263L, 1983 Summer (Box 64)
  - Write-up B-263L (Box 64)
  - BOT 263L Letters- Tropical Seaweeds (Box 64)
  - International Field Studies (B-263L) (Box 64)
  - B-219 and B-263L Cancellation letters (Box 64)
  - Acceptance letter B-263L (Box 64)
  - IFS-Bot 263L, 1984 Summer (Box 64)
  - BOT 263L All originals, 1984 Summer (Box 64)
  - BOT 263L Health Fee Waivers and copies of forms sent to RS (Box 64)
  - BOT 263L "Info Packets", 1984 Summer (Box 64)
  - BOT 263L, 1984 Summer (Box 64)
  - BOT 263L Inquiry/Applic. Response, 1984 Summer (Box 64)
  - BOT 263L Acceptance Letter, 1984 Summer (Box 64)
  - Report on 1989 Academic Programs and Comparative Data (Box 64)
  - DUML Auxillary Services Budget discussion, 2006 January 25 (Box 65)
  - unlabeled [planning/admin/reports], circa 2005
  - Nic School external review, circa 2000 (Box 65)
  - Report to the External review Team, 2000 January (Box 65)
  - Oversize Photographs, 8 folders (Box 66)
  - Oversize Photographs, 3 folders (Box 67)
  - Oversize Photographs, 6 folders (Box 68)